jottacloud.com 2019-03-13

# Jottacloud

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Jotta AS (Jottacloud). References to “we,” “our” and “us” refer to Jottacloud, while “you” and “your” refer to the Jottacloud customer or user.

### The Information We Collect

When you visit Jottacloud’s services and websites you provide us with two types of information: Personal Data you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us, and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our services.

### Information You Provide

When you register with Jottacloud, you provide us with your name, your email address and phone number hereinafter referred to as Personal Data.

Passwords are encrypted in our databases. We cannot read your password. Jottacloud does not have access to your credit card information. 

If you are a registered user of Jottacloud, you acknowledge and agree that Jottacloud may occasionally send you important communications regarding your account or the Service via email or SMS.

### Website Use Information

When you enter Jottacloud, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Jottacloud visitors and users. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that registered users are logged in. 

We use persistent cookies to store website usage information. Persistent cookies are stored on your computer for a longer period of time. Such information is not personally identifiable.

### Uploading Data

When you upload files to Jottacloud, you also send file system information, including names of files and directories. Files are encrypted with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) during transfer.

### How we use the Information

  * We use the information we collect for purposes of providing the users high quality services, and to develop new products and services for our customers and prospective customers.
  * We may view your file system metadata (filename, sizes etc. but not your file contents) to provide technical support.
  * We will not sell or market your email address.
  * We will not disclose your Personal Data to any third parties.
  * We will not view the files that you upload to Jottacloud. 

### Children under Age 13

Children under 13 are not allowed to register with Jottacloud. Jottacloud does not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13, or knowingly allow such persons to register. 

### Security

We use industry standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send sensitive Personal Data to us by email or instant messaging services.

If you cancel your account, your data and other information may be retained in our archive or backup record until deleted after 90 days.

### Links

Jottacloud may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Jottacloud.

### Access, Changes and Deletion of Personal Data 

You have the right to require access, correction or deletion of Personal Data we are processing. You also have the right to demand limited treatment, objection to treatment and claim the right to data portability. You may withdraw your consent for processing Personal Data at any time. 

You can read more about the content of these rights on the Data Inspectorate's website: [https://www.datatilsynet.no.](https://www.datatilsynet.no/)  

Your consent to store Personal Data is required to use our services.  

### Complaints

If you believe that our processing of Personal Data does not match what we have described here or we otherwise violate privacy laws, you may appeal to the Data Inspectorate. For information on how to contact the Data Inspectorate, visit the Data Inspectorate's website: [https://www.datatilsynet.no](https://www.datatilsynet.no/).

### Changes to this Policy

Jottacloud reserves the right in our sole discretion to revise, amend, or modify this policy at any time. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification of this policy will be posted on Jottacloud’s websites, and a User’s continued use of the Service will signify agreement to such changes. Notifications of the above-mentioned changes will be sent to the user via email.

### Links

Terms & Conditions  
Privacy Guarantee  
Transparency
